求你了  别打了
Please, stop.
你他妈说什么
What the hell did you say?
操
Fuck!
我让你靠近点
I said come closer.
怎么了
What happened?
这贱货把我鼻子咬掉了
Cocksucker bit my nose off.
去吧
Go.
你好  凯
Hello, Kai.
好久不见
It's been a while.
《黑吃黑》第三季 第九集
Banshee S03E09
坐  给你来杯咖啡
Have a seat. Let me get you some coffee.
我  还有事  我
I-- I can't stay. I just--
是来给你这个的
just came to drop this off.
离婚协议
Divorce papers.
嗯  今早调解办公室送来的
Yeah, they came from the mediator's office this morning.
我觉得你会想看看
Just figured that you'd want to take a look at them.
你看了吗
Did you?
还没有
Not yet, no.
那我们再等等吧
Maybe we should wait.
-什么意思  卡莉  -我不知道  我只是
- What do you mean, Carrie? - I don't know, I just--
我知道这是我们一起做的决定
I know this is what we decided.
可我现在不确定了  你呢
I'm not sure. Are you?
不  我也不确定
No. No, I'm not. I'm not sure.
很多事被我搞得一团糟
I made a mess of things.
是啊
Yeah, you did.
但你看  我
But listen, I've--
我想过这些年
I've had time to think about the pressure
你承受的压力
that you've been under all these years,
一直带着恐惧生活
the fear that you've been living with,
我知道你一定过得很难
and I know that must have been so hard.
你要是早点告诉我就好了
I just wish you could have told me.
我知道  真的对不起
I know. I'm so sorry.
我不想听你道歉
I don't want you to be sorry.
我不想再生活在过去了
I don't want to spend any more time looking back.
我们得向前看
We've got to look forward.
我想重新开始  你会不会觉得我疯了
Is it crazy to think that we could start over?
这个
Well...
对我们来说  疯的标准可是很高的
when it comes to crazy, I think we've set a pretty high bar.
要不这样
You know what?
协议书我先拿着吧
Why don't I hold on to these for a bit?
然后  我们顺其自然吧
And then, uh, we'll see how things go.
卡莉  该上菜了
Carrie, your order's up.
好  我得干活了
Okay. I've got to go.
去吧
Okay.
你知道  要想把这破地方弄安静
You know the only way to clean this rat trap
只能丢上一颗炸弹  对吧
is with a fucking grenade, right?
欢迎回家
Welcome home.
谢谢
Thanks.
南边的事搞定了吗
Everything get resolved down South?
对
Yeah.
你确定
You sure?
那可算是解脱了
Well, then, good riddance.
嗨  贾伯
Hey, Job.
嗨
Hey, yourself.
我们和好吧
We okay?
国防部宣布热那亚营正式停用了
DOD lists Camp Genoa as officially decommissioned.
没提我们的小晚会
There's no mention of our little soiree.
那挺好的
Well, that's great.
那我们和好吗
So we okay?
你差点把我害死
You almost got me killed.
-我知道  -我说过你没准备好
- I know. - I said you weren't ready.
-我求过你停止计划  -对不起
- I begged you to pull the plug. - I'm sorry.
而现在  我一点都不在乎你了
Well, right now, I don't give a fuck what you are.
你和我  有过不少交情
We got a lot of history, you and me.
也许现在都应该成为
Maybe that's all it should be--
历史
history.
谁他妈派你来的  操  我知道
Who the fuck sent you? Fuck it, I already know.
道尔顿跟你说我什么了
What did Dalton tell you about me?
他说你逾期了
That you're past your expiration date.
-你没问为什么吗  -我不在乎
- You didn't ask why? - I don't care.
等那个混蛋
You will when that
也让人把子弹射进你脑袋里  你就在乎了
motherfucker orders a bullet put in your brain.
想想吧  蠢货  最大的人民公敌不是我
Think, asshole. I ain't just public enemy number one.
我为你老板做了点事
I've done some shit for your boss
于是惹祸上身  成了隐患
that makes me a dangerous loose end.
等你杀了我  你也会变成隐患
As soon as you kill me, you become one, too.
-放屁  -是吗
- You're full of shit. - Am I?
你确定
You sure?
哥们儿  你自己去看看  自己看
Look, man. See for yourself. See for yourself.
看  他们来找你了
Look. Look. They're coming for you.
你来杀我  他们来杀你
You came for me, but they coming for you.
懂吗
All right?
我不知道你为你老板干了多少活
I don't know how many jobs you've done for your boss,
但这个  这是最后一次
but this right here, this one's the last one.
懂吗  你老板把你弃掉了
Okay? Your boss has written you off, all right?
他把你弃掉了  别别  听我说  等一下
He's written you off. Stop, stop. Listen to me. Wait, wait, wait.
他就是这种人  你知道的  不是吗
This is what he is. You know what he is, all right?
听我说  我说的是实话  你知道的
Listen to me, I'm telling you the truth and you know it.
想想  想想吧兄弟
Think. Think, man.
道尔顿在大清洗  我们都死定了
Dalton's cleaning house. We both dead.
你说的那是你
Speak for yourself.
稳住  稳住  你不能把我扔下
Hold up, hold up. You can't leave me here.
-等着瞧吧  -我靠  听我说
- Watch me. - Fuck that. Listen to me.
考虑长远点
You thinking about long-term survival,
有些重要的事  只有我能告诉你
you need to know the things only I can tell you.
你知道我说的是实话
Come on, you know what I'm saying is true.
我能帮你
I can help you.
-你叫什么  -贾伯
- What's your name? - Job.
好吧  贾伯  跟紧我
All right, Job, you stay close.
一旦落队  你就自生自灭吧
You fall behind, you're on your own.
弗拉奇尔  这他妈什么情况
Frazier, what the hell is this?
我们沟通比较少
We don't talk much.
我觉得应该来报个到
I figured it was time to check in.
他妈的可以打电话啊
You could have picked up the fucking phone.
没错  你也可以在决定违反
Yeah, well, you could have, too,
我们的协议  让你侄女给萨尔瓦多人
before you decided to renege on our agreement
卖货前  给我打个电话
and let your niece sell to the Salvadorans.
你他妈说什么呢
What the fuck are you talking about?
不好意思  你刚才说什么
I'm sorry, what was that?
-没什么  -很好
- Nothing. - Good.
无凭无据的反驳不适合你  凯
Flimsy denials don't suit you, Kai.
你一向有话直说
You've always been a straight talker.
你让你的走狗们回避
Why don't you call off your dogs
咱们讨论一下需要讨论的事  怎么样
and let us discuss what needs discussing?
如果我们早这么处理就好了  对吧
It would be nice if things worked that way, wouldn't it?
但很可惜  我们这个行业就是如此讽刺
But unfortunately, that is the sad irony of our business.
我们现在可以好好谈了
By the time we get to talk like this,
但已经没什么好谈的了
there's nothing left to discuss.
你肯定知道我会如何对待
You must have known how I'd react
如此背叛我的人
to a betrayal of this magnitude.
你也会这样  对吧
Exactly like you would, yes?
开个价吧  弗拉奇尔  多少都给你
Just name your price, Frazier, you got it.
这不是多少钱的问题
This isn't about money.
一切都是钱的问题
Everything is about money.
这次不一样
Not this time.
我从来不把赫克托·莫拉莱斯放在眼里
Hector Morales has always been dirt on the bottom of my shoe.
但有你给他撑腰
But with you by his side,
那个油腔滑调的臭娘炮
that greasy, cocksucking motherfucker
可能真会威胁到我
could become a considerable threat.
这我可不允许
And I can't allow that.
弗拉奇尔  这次你错了
Frazier, you're making a mistake.
我曾对你深怀期待  凯
I expected more from you, Kai.
这得怪我
Shame on me.
就剩两件事可做了  凯
There's only two things left for you to do, Kai.
给我道歉  然后去死
And that's apologize and die.
老子要亲手割开
I'm gonna slit your throat
你这畜生的喉咙
like a fucking cow.
我要听到他惨叫
I want to hear him scream.
再打
Again.
给我站起来  起来
Get your ass-- get up.
趴下
Get down!
胡德
Hood!
-小姐  你不能这么闯进来  -别碰我
- Miss, you can't just come in here. - Don't touch me.
-没事的  邦克  -抱歉  警长
- It's okay, Bunker. - Sorry, sir.
-他们把我叔叔带走了  -他们是谁
- They took my uncle. - They?
-"黑胡子"  -谁
- The Black Beards. - Who?
费城的犯罪团伙
They're a crime syndicate from Philadelphia.
这关我什么事呢
And this is my problem because...?
他们要杀了我叔叔
They're going to kill him.
我帮不了你
I can't help you.
感谢你来找我
Thanks for stopping by.
洛特斯副警长
Deputy Lotus.
该死的普罗科特  我们要怎么办
Fucking Proctor, huh? What are we gonna do about it?
-什么也不做  -你说什么
- We're not gonna do anything. - What are you talking about?
-我他妈才不爱管普罗科特  -我也是
- I don't give a shit about Proctor. - Neither do I.
但那个疯侄女说我前妻艾米丽也被带走了
But the crazy niece, she told me they also took my ex-wife Emily.
什么  她跟普罗科特怎么扯上关系了
What? What does she have to do with Proctor?
她之前在照顾普罗科特的妈妈
She took care of his mother.
-他老妈死了  布罗克  -我知道
- His mother's dead, Brock. - I know.
他俩
They, uh...
你他妈是在逗我吧
You've got to be fucking kidding me.
可不是嘛
Yeah, tell me about it.
我让邦克和瑞文去设检查站
Alright, look, I'm gonna have Bunker and Raven set up checkpoints.
然后联系州警  挨家挨户...
We'll call the state police. We're gonna go door-to-door--
用不着了  他们可能早走远了
No, no, no, they're probably long gone by now.
也可能还没走  对吧  我们得行动起来
Maybe they're not, all right? We've gotta do something.
布罗克  这事别拖我下水
Brock, I'm not gonna get involved.
你听我说  胡德
No, listen to me, Hood!
我不止一次为你赴汤蹈火了
I have put my ass on the line for you more than once, all right?
现在我求你
Now I'm asking you...
拜托了
Please.
我没空
I'm not here.
听着  我没别的选择了
Listen, I wouldn't ask if I had another choice,
拜托你帮我个忙
but I need some help.
等下  等等  等等
Hold up. Hold up. Hang on. Hold up.
天呐  没人追  你把他们都杀了
God. It's okay, you killed them all.
有几个你还补了一枪
I think you killed some of them twice,
你杀人杀开心了吧混蛋
you trigger-happy son of a bitch.
还会有人来的  我们得赶快走
There's gonna be more of them. We need to keep moving.
我喘不上气了
I need a little oxygen.
操
Fuck.
你他妈都不用喘气吗
How the fuck are you not even winded?
我们都跑了三英里了
We just ran, like, three miles.
我的脚要疼死了
My feet are fucking killing me.
少说点话就能喘上气了
Talk less, you can breathe more.
听着  "牛仔铁汉"
I'll tell you what, Clint Eastwood,
你回答问题  我就闭嘴
I'll shut the fuck up when you answer me this--
我们这他妈是要去哪
where the fuck are we going?
我们得避开大路
We need to get off the street.
快走
Move.
你没回答我问题
You didn't answer my question.
去我那儿吧
I got a place.
我查看了斯特林安保公司
I reviewed the digital security logs
弗吉尼亚总部的安全日志
from Sterling Safe's headquarters in Virginia.
没有明显的主机违约
No obvious mainframe breaches,
也没有病毒  或者外部的暴力解码
no embedded viruses or brute force attacks from the outside.
所以我转而检视内部问题
That's why I looked for something a little bit more inside.
斯特林公司会仔细审查每个外包商
Sterling meticulously vets all private contractors.
审查过程长达数月  所以不可能突然
The process takes a month, so the sudden addition
更换了两个维护人员
of two new maintenance workers didn't make sense,
而且还在24小时后又开除了
especially since they were deleted less than 24 hours later.
-是他们的疏忽么  -并不是  我够幸运
- They made a mistake? - No, I just got lucky.
文件被打乱并篡改
The files were scrubbed and overwritten.
如果不是突然的电涌引发了
I would never have found them if not for a power surge
站外数据备份  我不可能找到他们
that triggered an off-site data backup.
这是糖果·贝茨
That's Sugar Bates.
前获奖拳手  现在本地经营酒吧  有案底
Ex-prizefighter, local bartender, and an ex-con.
-抢劫过  -故意伤人
- Robbery? - Aggravated assault.
贝茨先生只会以力取胜  缺少计谋
Mr. Bates solves his problems with brute force, not skill.
-这是当晚的司机  -他是谁
- He was the van driver. - Who's that?
这就是问题所在  对吧
Well, that's the question, isn't it?
我交叉比对了所有面部识别数据库的数据
I cross-referenced every facial recognition database there is--
包括国安局  中国国安部  以色列摩萨德
NSA, MSS, Mossad.
要么就是这货躲过了所有
Either this guy is completely invisible
监控摄像头和间谍卫星的监视
to all surveillance cameras and spy satellites,
要么就是他黑进了
or he's managed to exploit
世界上最先进的电脑安全网络
the most secure computer systems ever designed.
他是个黑客
He's a hacker.
不出意外的话  他是那位黑客
If I'm right, he's the hacker.
网端狂热者的一员  中情局追踪多年无果
CIA's been chasing their tails for years trying to find this guy.
黑客们的偶像  人称贾伯
The online fanboys, they call him Job.
但没人知道他的真实身份
But nobody knows for sure who he really is.
你找到他了
You find him?
在过去的12小时
Over the last 12 hours,
他的手机发出的微弱信号
there's been a flurry of cellular activity,
显示区号是215
all originating from phones registered to the 215 area code.
费城
Philadelphia.
信号发出地在城南
Transmissions are localized to the towers to the south.
那儿有很多建筑
There's a lot of buildings there,
但只有一座废弃的高中
but only one abandoned high school.
-地址是  -广溪路57号
- Address? - 57 Broad Creek Road.
好
Okay.
贾伯
Listen, Job--
这是最后一次帮你
This was the last time.
瞧  你不是也不行了
Well, look who's finally winded.
我天  你中弹了
Jesus Christ, you're hit.
快从我的博夫曼沙发上起来
Get the fuck off my Baughman chair.
你知不知道把你的血
Do you know how hard it is
从雪呢绒上弄掉有多难
to get blood out of chenille upholstery?
行行好  把嘴闭上好么
Hey, do me a favor. Shut the fuck up, would you?
别动
Stay here.
没人知道这儿
This place is completely off the grid.
如果道尔顿知道的话  他在给你
If Dalton knew about it, don't you think he would have told you
任务的时候  就告诉你了
when he gave you your marching orders?
你在道尔顿手下多久了
How long you been under Dalton's thumb?
很久了  你怎么认识他
Too long. How do you know him?
我技术高超  但遇人不淑
I have a unique skill set. In a rare lapse in judgment,
给你前老板打工
I rendered services to your former boss,
还觉得他是个人物
thinking he was the real deal.
他不是么
He wasn't?
他们从来不是
Well, they never are.
我现在服务罪犯
I stick to criminals now.
和他们一起至少不用太担心
At least you know where you stand with a criminal.
那你怎么了
So what's your story?
我来猜猜
Let me guess.
道尔顿在你不顺的时候找上你
Dalton got to you when you were at rock bottom.
和你说他能让你更有价值
Told you he could make you something more.
这种人总有办法说服别人
Man does have a way of getting inside your head.
而且只对我们这些牛人有效
Happens to the best of us.
你说你能帮我摆脱他
You said you could help me get away from him.
要怎么做
How?
他找不到  所以杀不了
He can't kill us if he can't find us.
-他会找到我的  -试试看咯
- He can find me. - He can try.
他能通过卫星  数据库
He got access to satellites, databases,
定制软件来定位一个人
and custom software that can locate almost anybody anywhere.
但你猜猜  那些东西是谁设计的
But who the fuck do you think designed that software?
等我完成了我该做的事
By the time I'm done doing my thing,
你就会变成无迹可寻的幽灵
you are going to be a fucking ghost.
先从名字开始
Now, let's start with your name.
我们是警察  放下武器  放下
Sheriff's Department! Drop your weapons. Drop 'em!
-给我放下  -放下你的枪
- Put 'em down! - Drop your gun.
-去你的  -布罗克
- Fuck you. - Brock!
-艾米丽  你没事吧  -她很好
- Emily, you all right? - She's fine.
-暂时的  -你敢碰她你死定了
- For now. - You touched her, you're a dead man.
一个快要被打成马蜂窝的人
Those are tough words coming from a man
还敢口出狂言
who's about to get shot full of holes.
-彼此彼此  -都别开枪
- Yeah, right back at you. - Nobody's getting shot.
-胡德  -终于有个有脑子的了
- Hood. - Now, there's a voice of reason.
-请问你是  -卢卡斯·胡德警长
- And you are? - Sheriff Lucas Hood.
警长吗
Sheriff.
那好吧  胡德警长
Well, then, Sheriff Hood,
你有什么解决办法吗
do you have a solution in mind?
我们只救这个女人
We're only here for the woman.
那普罗科特先生呢
And Mr. Proctor?
你跟他有什么过节
Whatever's going on between you and him,
那是你的事  我不管
that's your business.
说的真好  我简直不敢相信
Now, that sounds too good to be true.
达成共识了吗
Do we have a deal?
放那个女孩走
Let the girl go.
等等  你到底在说什么
Wait, what the hell are you talking about?
-你不能这样做  -艾米丽  我们走
- You can't do that. - Emily, let's go.
-不  我不走  -艾米丽
- No, I'm not leaving. - Emily!
-他们会弄死他的  -要滚快滚
- They're gonna kill him. - Get the fuck out!
我们走  艾米丽  走吧
Let's go. Emily, come on.
快  我们走  快点
Come on. Let's go, come on.
很好  我们走吧
It's all right. Come on, let's go.
卧槽
Oh, shit.
-你跟踪我们  -我叔叔在哪
- What, did you follow us? - Where's my uncle?
走啊
Come on.
什么  你竟然没救他出来
Wait, did you just leave him in there?
-我们走  -搞什么鬼
- Let's go. - What the fuck?!
快走  跟我走
Come on. Let's go.
雷诺克斯说你推荐你侄女丽贝卡
Lennox tells me you're grooming your niece Rebecca
当你的接班人
to be your successor.
我们要看看她能否胜任
We'll have to see if she's up for the task.
我会为你的灵魂祈祷  凯
I will pray for your soul, Kai.
不过我觉得现在
But I think at this point,
即使是上帝也不知道如何拯救你
even God doesn't know what to make of you.
安息吧  老朋友
Rest in peace, old friend.
把门锁上
Lock the door.
非常乐意为您效劳
I'm gonna enjoy this.
我也是
Me, too.
博登
Burton!
杀了他
Shoot him off.
叔叔
Uncle!
他们本想烧死我
They were going to burn me.
在我母亲去世后
After my mother died...
我以为上帝是仁慈的
I thought that I felt the grace of God.
他要召唤我回去
I thought he was calling me back.
可那不是上帝
That wasn't God.
只是因为悲痛
That was just grief.
和空虚感
An emptiness.
他们失脚的时候
To me belong vengeance and recompense.
《圣经》《申命记》第32章
伸冤报应在我
Their foot shall slide in due time.
因他们遭灾的日子近了
The day of their calamity is at hand.
那要临在他们身上的
And the things that shall come upon them
必速速来到
make haste.
对不起  母亲
等等
Hey.
站住别动
Hey, stay where you are.
嗨  别跑
Hey. Hey, hey, hey. Stop.
我要和警长谈
I need to talk to the sheriff.
-你会跟他见面的  -你不明白
- Yeah, you can talk to him. - You don't understand.
-他认识我  -你叫什么名字
- He knows me. - What's your name?
蒂法·霍普韦尔
Deva Hopewell.
-你是镇长的孩子  -是的
- You the mayor's kid? - Yes.
嗨  霍普韦尔小姐  别跑
Hey, hey, hey. Miss Hopewell. Hey, hey, stop.
霍普韦尔小姐  你被捕了
Miss Hopewell, you are under arrest.
你有权保持沉默
You have the right to remain silent.
你所说或所做的一切
Anything you say or do
都将成为呈堂证供
will be held against you in a court of law.
-这些事需要时间  -是的
- These things take time. - Yeah.
我能应付的来
I can handle it.
-你可以吗  -大多数时候
- Can you? - Most of the time.
这他妈什么情况
What the fuck is this?
贾斯帕  布莱斯
Jasper, Bryce.
老天爷  邦克  你做条子了
Jesus Christ, Bunker. You're a fucking pig?
我是女妖镇副警长
I'm a Banshee deputy sheriff.
你是他妈的叛徒
You're a motherfucking traitor.
我真该朝你心脏戳一刀
I should stab you through the heart.
表达你的观点不犯法
Expressing your opinion isn't a crime,
但威胁警官就不行了
but threatening a peace officer is.
那在哈里斯堡欺负人也是违法的啊
So was torching that kike temple in Harrisburg,
但我记得你也照做不误了
but I don't remember that stopping you.
-还是加尔文管事吗  -必须的啊
- Calvin still running things? - Damn straight he is.
但如果你觉得他会护着你
But if you think he's gonna protect you from us,
那你就想多了
you got another think coming.
加尔文应该在他有机会的时候就杀了你
Calvin should have killed you when he had the chance.
你告诉我兄弟  我会很快见到他的
You tell my brother I'll be seeing him real soon.
谢谢
Thank you, boys.
你是上校  是吧
Why, Colonel, right?
你也当过兵吗
Were you a military man?
不是  只是看过很多电影
No, just watch a lot of movies.
想喝什么
What's your poison?
美格纯正波本  不加冰
Maker's Mark, neat.
在女巫镇这么久了
All this time in Banshee
我还从来没来过这里
and I've never been in here before.
这里嘛
Well, it's...
没什么讲究的
not much to look at,
只是勉强能住而已
but at least the roof doesn't leak.
嗯
Hmm.
有一天发生了件疯狂的事
You know, the craziest thing happened the other day.
-真的吗  -嗯
- Did it? - Mmm.
四个傻逼决定
Four idiots decided to steal
从我那儿偷钱  一大笔钱
a considerable amount of my money.
还有这事
Is that so?
但这还不是最疯狂的呢
Mm, but that's not the crazy part.
这些人还觉得能逃之夭夭
These guys actually thought they were gonna get away with it.
你这样是两败俱伤啊
See, what you have here is a lose-lose situation.
我从来不会输
I never lose.
妈的
Damn it!
谢谢你的酒
Thanks for the drink.
操你妈
Fuck you.
贾伯
Job.
你他妈是谁
Who the fuck are you?
我叫利奥  也许你听说过我
My name is Leo. Maybe you've heard of me.
别装逼
Don't flatter yourself.
我听说过你  贾伯
Well, I've definitely heard of you, Job.
所以我用了两倍的镇静剂
That's why I doubled the sedative.
此时此刻对我来说很重要
This is actually a very big moment for me.
-你要回去救他  -不  小艾  我不去
- You have to go back for him. - No, Em, I don't.
-别闹了  -那我去
- Now come on. - Well, then I will.
听我说  小艾
The hell you are. Em, listen to me. Listen.
你知道你今晚离死亡有多近吗
Do you have any idea how close you came to dying tonight?
他们会因为他杀了你的
They were going to kill you because of him.
-放开我  -天哪
- Let go of me! - Jesus Christ!
醒醒
Open your eyes!
你明白吗  你他妈的和一个变态搞在了一起
Do you understand? You are shacking up with a fucking psychopath.
所以你因为嫉妒要让他死吗
What, you're going to let him die because you're jealous?
去你妈的  布罗克  你个懦夫
Fuck you, Brock! You coward.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
我操
Oh, fuck!
不用谢我他妈救你一命
And you're welcome for saving your goddamn life.
先生
Sir.
她在哪里
Where is she?
需要您在这份报告上签字
I just need your signature on this report
就可以带您女儿回家了
and you can take your daughter home.
-她不回家  -什么
- She's not going home. - What?
至少今晚不行
At least not tonight.
好的
Yes, sir.
抱歉  蒂法  我不知道还能怎么办
I'm sorry, Deva. I don't know what else to do.
爸爸
Dad.
Dad!
谢天谢地
Thank God.
我还以为你死了  快过来
I thought you were dead. Come on.
好吧  得送你去医院
Okay, we're gonna have to get you to the hospital.
绝对不能去医院
We're not going to any hospital.
-为什么  -我犯错了
- Why? - I made a mistake.
我不应该让事情到了这个地步
I should never have allowed things to go this far.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
我们不能再见面了
You and I will never see each other again.
我不明白
I-- I don't understand.
谢谢你对我母亲那么好
Thank you for your services to my mother.
我会好好补偿你的辛劳
You'll be compensated for your time and trouble.
别这样  凯
Wait, don't do this, Kai.
我知道你是想保护我
I know you're trying to protect me,
但只要跟你在一起  我就不怕他们
but I'm not afraid of those men when I'm with you.
再见
Good-bye.
你该怕的不是他们
It's not those men you need to be afraid of.
我知道你也许很难相信
I know this might be hard to believe,
但是你父亲觉得这样才是为你好
but your father thinks he's doing what's best for you.
他不是我父亲
He's not really my father.
邦克
Bunker.
长官  霍普韦尔小姐必须留下来
Sir, Miss Hopewell is being held for possession.
把钥匙给我
Give me the keys.
快走
Let's go.
我很尊敬你  长官
With all due respect, sir,
但是霍普韦尔镇长希望她留下来过夜
mayor Hopewell wanted her to stay overnight.
我不在乎他想干什么  快走
I don't give a shit what he wants. Let's go.
有东西吗  我带你回去
You got any stuff? I'll take you home.
抱歉吵醒了你  我没忍住
Sorry to wake you. I just couldn't help myself.
我得承认  我可能是你的头号粉丝
I must admit, I am probably your biggest fan.
你他妈要是想要我的签名
If you wanted my autograph, motherfucker,
张个嘴就行
all you had to do was ask.
再说吧
Maybe later.
别浪费力气  回头用得着
Save your strength. You're going to need it.
事情的展开真是奇妙
It's funny how things work out.
你不觉得吗
Don't you think?
不过我很好奇
I am curious, though.
你决定偷我的钱  是什么时候
Was the decision to steal my money made before or--
跟我上床之前还是之后
or after you spread your legs for me?
你真觉得我会自愿跟你睡吗
Do you really think I'd fuck you if I didn't have to?
把你的同伙供出来
Give me the name of your fourth,
我就让你少受点苦
and I'll keep your suffering to a minimum.
不要
No.
把名字说出来
Give me a fucking name now.
去你妈的
Fuck you.
不管怎样  我会找到你在保护的人
One way or another, I will find the person you're protecting.
问题在于
Only question is, how much
等我找到的时候  你会变成几块
of you is going to be left by the time I do?
搞什么  胡德  你没权利带蒂法回家
What the fuck, Hood? You had no right taking Deva home.
你听我说  你他妈离我女儿远点
Now you listen to me. You stay the hell away from my daughter.
5.56口径北约绿尖子弹
5.56 NATO Green Tip.
安娜在哪里
Where's Ana?
-什么  -你妻子在哪里
- What? - Where is your wife?
操他妈的  你又做了什么
Jesus Christ, what the fuck did you do now?